Finding Aid for the Edwin Hamlett Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Miscellaneous Organizations
  - Race Relations Information Center: Newsletter: Legal Size (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Special Reports (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Special Reports (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Special Reports (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Race Relations Information Center: Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Race Relations Institute at Fisk (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Repeal the Draft: General History (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Repeal the Draft: Memos (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Repeal the Draft: Correspondence Outgoing (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Repeal the Draft: Pamphlets (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Repeal the Draft: Newsletters (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Pamphlets (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Releases (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Highlander Reports (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Reports/Articles (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Notes (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Notes 1 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Notes 2 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Notes 3 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Report and Writing by Ed Hamlett (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: News (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Save Our Cumberland Mountains: Legal Size Materials (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Socialist Youths (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Southern Legal Action Movement (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Southwestern Company (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Strengthening the New Policies Conference (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Tennessee Churchmen for Abolition of Capital Punishment (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Tennessee Commission for Human Development (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Tennessee Commission for Human Development (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Tennessee Commission for Human Development (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Tennessee Commission for Human Development (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - United Mineworkers of America (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - University Christian Movement (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - US/China People’s Friendship Association (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Vietnam: Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam: Memos (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam: Pamphlets (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Vietnam: Pamphlets (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam: Statements (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam: Articles (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam: Articles “A Citizen’s White Paper on American Policy in Vietnam” (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Vietnam: Publications (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Vietnam: Publications “War Within Man” and “The Significance of the State Department White Paper on Vietnam (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Vietnam: Newsletters, Aug. 26, 1965; National Vietnam Newsletter (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Vietnam: Vietnam Day Conference (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Vietnam Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Vietnam: Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Vietnam: Legal Size Materials (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Vietnam: Newspaper Clippings (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Council on Human Relations (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Council on Human Relations (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Voting (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - W.E.B. Dubois Clubs of America (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Wedge (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Great Speckled Bird
  - 1:1, Mar. 15-28 1968 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - 1:3, Apr. 12-25, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - 1:4, Apr. 26-May 9 1968 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - 1:5, May 10-23 1968 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - 1:6, May 24- Jun. 6, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - 1:7, Jun. 7-20 1968 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - 1:8, Jun. 21- Jul. 2, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - 1:9, Jul. 3-18 1968 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - 1:10, Jul. 19- Aug. 1, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - 1:11, Aug. 2- 15 1968 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - 1:12, Aug 16-29 1968 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - 1:13, Aug. 30- Sept. 12, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - 1:15, Sept. 23, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - 1:17, Oct. 7, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - 1:19, Oct. 21, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - 1:20, Oct. 28, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - 1:22, Nov. 11, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - 1:25, Dec. 9, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - 1:26, Dec. 13, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - 1:29, Jan. 13, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - 1:30, Jan. 20, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - 1:32, Feb. 7- Feb. 13, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - 1:34, Feb. 17, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - 1:35, Feb. 24, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - 1:39, Feb. 28, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - 1:37, Mar. 10, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - 1:39, Mar. 24, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - 2:6, Apr. 21, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - 2:8, May 5, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - 2:12, Jun. 2, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - 2:14, Jun. 16, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - 2:16, Jun 30, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - 2:18, Jul. 14, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - 2:23, Aug. 18, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - 2:24, Aug. 25, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - 2:27, Sept. 15, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - 2:29, Sept. 29. 1969 (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - 2:30, Oct. 6, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - 2:31, Oct. 13, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - 2:33, Oct. 27, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - 2:35, Nov. 10, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - 2:36, Nov. 17, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - 2:36, Nov. 17, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - 2:40, Dec. 15, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 44)
  - 3:1, Jan. 5, 1970; (Graphics Issue) (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - 3:2, Jan. 5, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - 3:4, Jan. 26, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - 3:5, Feb. 2, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - 3:6, Feb. 9, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 49)
  - 3:7, Feb. 16, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - 3:8, Feb. 23, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 51)
  - 3:9, Mar. 2, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 52)
  - 3:10, Mar. 9, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 53)
  - 3:13, Mar. 30, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 54)
  - 3:14, Apr. 2, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 55)
  - 3:15, Apr. 13, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 56)
  - 3:16, Apr. 20, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 57)
  - 3:17, Apr. 27, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 58)
  - 3:18, May 4, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 59)
  - 3:19, May 11, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 60)
  - 3:20, May 18, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 61)
  - 3:21, May 25, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 62)
  - 3:23, Jun. 8, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 63)
  - 3:25, Jun. 22, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 64)
  - 3:26, Jun. 29, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 65)
  - 3:27, Jul. 6, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 66)
  - 3:28, Jul. 13, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 67)
  - 3:29, Jul. 20, 1970; (Incorrectly printed as 4:29) (Box 71, Folder 68)
  - 3:30, Jul. 27, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 69)
  - 3:31, Aug. 3, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 70)
  - 3:32, Aug. 10, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 71)
  - 3:33, Aug. 17, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 72)
  - 3:34, Aug. 24, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 73)
  - 3:25, Aug. 31, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 74)
  - 3:37, Sept. 14, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 75)
  - 3:38, Sept. 21, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 76)
  - 3:48, Nov. 30, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 77)
  - 4:4, Jan. 25, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 78)
  - 4:6, Feb. 8, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 79)
  - 4:7, Feb. 15, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 80)
  - 4:8, Feb. 22, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 81)
  - 4:9, Mar. 1, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 82)
  - 4:13, Mar. 29, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 83)
  - 4:14, Apr. 5, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 84)
  - 4:15, Apr. 12, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 85)
  - 4:16, Apr. 19, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 86)
  - 4:17, Apr. 26, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 87)
  - 4:18, May 3, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 88)
  - 4:19, May 10, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 89)
  - 4:20, May 17, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 90)
  - 4:21, May 24, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 91)
  - 4:23, Jun. 7, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 92)
  - 4:24, Jun. 14, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 93)
  - 4:25, Jun. 21, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 94)
  - 4:26, Jun. 28, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 95)
  - 4:28, Jul. 12, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 96)
  - 4:29, Jul. 19, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 97)
  - 4:30, Jul. 26, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 98)
  - 4:31, Aug. 2, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 99)
  - 4:32, Aug. 9, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 100)
  - 4:33, Aug. 15, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 101)
  - 4:34, Aug. 23, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 102)
  - 4:35, Aug. 30, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 103)
  - 4:36, Sept. 6, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 104)
  - 4:37, Sept. 13, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 105)
  - 4:38, Sept. 20, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 106)
  - 4:39, Sept. 27, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 107)
  - 4:40, Oct. 4, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 108)
  - 4:41, Oct. 11, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 109)
  - 4:42, Oct. 18, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 110)
  - 4:43, Oct. 25, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 111)
  - 4:44, Nov. 1, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 112)
  - 4:45, Nov. 8, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 113)
  - 4:46, Nov. 15, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 114)
  - 4:47, Nov. 22, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 115)
  - 4:48, Nov. 29, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 116)
  - 4:49, Dec. 6, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 117)
  - 4:50, Dec. 13, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 118)
  - 4:51, Dec. 20, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 119)
  - 4:52, Dec. 27, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 120)
  - 5:1, Jan. 10, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - 5:2, Jan. 17, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - 5:3, Jan. 24, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - 5:6, Feb. 14, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - 5:7, Feb. 21, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - 5:9, Mar. 6, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - 5:10, Mar. 13, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - 5:12, Mar. 27, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - 5:14, Apr. 10, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - 5:32, Aug. 14, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - 5:34, Aug. 28, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - 5:44, Nov. 6, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - 6:12, Apr. 2, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - 6:14, Apr. 16, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - 6:15, Apr. 23, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - 6:18, May 14, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - 6:19, May 21, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - 6:21, Jun. 4, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - 6:28, Jul. 23, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - 6:30, Aug. 6, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - 6:42, Nov. 5, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - 7:23, Jun. 10, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - 7:26, Jul. 1, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Publications:
  - 2nd Look, Mar.- May 1968 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - 7 Days: Apr. and Jun. 1978 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - 7 Days: Sept. and Oct. 1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - 7 Days: Nov. and Dec. 1978 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - 7 Days: Feb. and Mar. 1979 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - 7 Days: Mar. and Apr. 1979 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - 7 Days: May and Sept 1979 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - 40 Acres and a Mule, Nov.- Dec. 1979 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - 40 Acres and a Mule, Jan. 1980 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - 40 Acres and a Mule, Feb. 1980 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - 40 Acres and a Mule, Feb. 1980 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - ACLU: Civil Liberties (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Adventure Hope: Christians and the Crisis in Central America (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - AEE Energy Books Catalogue (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Against Racism 1:1 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Against the Social Chauvinist Theory of Directing (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - America’s Need: Social Services and Jobs (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Appalachia (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Appalachian Issues and Resources, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Appalachian Mountain Books #4, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - APSC, Nov. 1971 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - AKA Sorority “Negro Women in the Judiciary” (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Arkansas Schools and Communities, 1991-1992 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Arkansas Schools (miscellaneous) (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Atlantic, Sept. 1961 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - ATO: Spring 1994 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Avatar, Dec. 8- 21 no. 14 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Avatar, Jan. 5-18 no. 15 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Billy Graham New York Crusade: Souvenir Edition (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Black Liberation Struggle (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Book Catalogues: Various (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Brother, Apr. 1971, Summer 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Brother, Apr. 1973 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Buckeye Music News, Oct. 1969 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Buford Pusser Booklet (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Burning Spear, Jul. 1978 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Call, Jan. 17, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Campus Illustrated, Oct. 1961 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Canadian Dimension, Oct./Nov. 1970 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Canyon Collective (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Workers, May 1965 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - CCLC Legislative Newsletter (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Challenge, Jul. 13, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Christianity and Crisis (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - CNVA Bulletin, May 1962 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Cock Rock (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Committee of Returned Peace Corps Volunteers (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Common Sense: vol. 1 no. 13 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Commune: by P. Guillarme (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Community College (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Consumer Reports, Jun. 1970 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Consumer Reports, Feb. 1990 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Convener vol. 1 no. 2 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Country Corner, Sept. 1969 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Country Hotline News, Mar. 1972 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Country Music, Nov. 1972 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Country Music Gazette, Oct. 1969 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Country Sky, Oct. 1971- May 1972 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Country Sky, Aug. 1972 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Covenant Group for Lifestyle Assessment (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Crawdaddy vol. IV no. 6 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Cumberland College Catalogue, 1971/1972 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - “Cybernation Christmas or Crisis” by Dale Caldwell (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - “Cybernation and Human Rights,” and “Cybernation and Fulfillment of Man” (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Daily World (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Dandelion: Winter, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - DC Gazette, May 1970 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - “Democracy in the University” and “How the University Fails Society” (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Dollars and Cents (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Dollars and Cents, Oct. 1975 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Dome, Sept. 1988 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Economic Priorities Report, Mar./Apr. 1972 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Energy Management Survey (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Epworth Ministry (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Eugene McCarthy on the Record (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Explorer: Vol. 43, 4 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Face to Face, Jun. 1969 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Fag Rag Thirteen: Summer, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Family Circle, Nov. 2, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Family of Man, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Father was a Housewife (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Fighting Poverty and City Hall, Jun. 3, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Finger, Sept. 1969 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Fordian, Dec. 20, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Fordian, Oct 1979 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Free Student: no. 3 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Freeze, Oct. 1987 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Gay Liberation (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Gazette, Feb./Mar. 1978, and Aug./Sept. 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Grass Roots, Jul. 1974 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Guardian, Mar. 1968 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Guardian: Special Supplement, Jun. 1977 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Guidebook of Greenfield Village, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Hank, Aug. 1977 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Hard Work (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Harpers, Sept. 1959 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Historic Nashville (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - “Housing and Urban Renewal” (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Human Rights and Economic Development (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Hunger USA Revisited (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - “Improving the Quality of Urban Life” (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - In These Times, Jan. 10-16, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - In These Times, Jan. 17-23, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - In These Times, Jan. 24-30, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - In These Times, Jan. 31- Feb. 6, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - In These Times, Feb. 7-13, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - In These Times, Feb. 14-20, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - In These Times, Feb. 21-27, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - In These Times, Feb. 28- Mar. 6, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Instructor, Oct. 1990 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Insurgent (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Internal Migration and Full Employment in the US, 1945 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Invest in the USA (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Ivory Tower MN Daily, Mar. 27, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Ф Journal (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Jack Benny (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Jazz Age Chronicles (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Winter, 1967-1968 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Spring, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Winter, 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Fall, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Winter/Spring, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Fall, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Spring, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Winter, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Journal of the Committee of Southern Churchmen: Fall/Winter, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Key to the Library (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Know Your Communist Enemy: 1 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Know Your Communist Enemy: 2 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Know Your Communist Enemy: 3 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Labor Today, Mar. 1969 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Labor Today, May 1969 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Lancer: Fall, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Last Post, Oct. 1970 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Left Face, Apr. 1971 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Leviathan, Apr. 1969 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Leviathan, Jun. 1970 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Lexington Voice: Vol. 1 Nos. 2 and 4 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Lexington Voice: Vol. 1 Nos. 6 and 7 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Liberation, Jun./Jul. 1965 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Liberation, May 1969 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Liberation, Apr. 1970 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Liberation, Jan. 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Little Rock City Services, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Looking Forward: “Protest to Politics,” Feb. 1965 and “Roots of Dominican Crisis,”, May 1965 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Maine Photographic Workshops (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - “Majority Black School Districts in the 11 Southern States” (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - MANNA (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King and the Montgomery Story (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Marxism: University Women and Feminism Issues in the Economy (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Marxist Bulletin: no. 9 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Mass Media and Race Relations Report (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - MCN Gospel News (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Mid-South, Feb. 11, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Militant, May 1965 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Mississippi Free Lance, Apr.- Sept. 1969 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Mississippi Free Press, Oct. 1969- Feb. 1970 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Modern Maturity, Aug./Sept. 1992 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Modern Utopian: A Way Out (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Mother Jones, Feb./Mar. 1979 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Motive, Mar. 1965 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Motive, Nov. 1969 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Motive, Dec. 1969 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Motive, Jan. 1970 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Motive, Feb. 1970 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Motive, Mar. 1970 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Motive, Apr./May 1970 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Motive, Dec. 1970 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Motive, Mar. 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Motive, Apr./May 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Motorist, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Mountain Life and Work (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Music City News, Sept. 1969 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Music City News, Oct. 1969 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Music City News, Oct. 1969 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - NACLA Report, Nov./Dec. 1983 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Nameless Newsprint: vol. 1 no. 9 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Nashville, Jan. 1979 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Nashville in a Nutshell, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Nashville Sounds by Kevin Reid (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - National Forest Vacations (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Navajo Nation (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - New America, Jul. 1965, Dec. 1965 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - New American Movement, Mar. 1972 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - New American Movement, Sept. 1972 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - New American Movement, Oct. 1972 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - New American Movement, Mar.- Apr. 1972 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - New Economic Policy (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - New Foundation, Apr.- May 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - New Foundation, Jul.- Sept. 1969 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - New Foundation, Oct. 1969- Feb. 1970 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - New Guard (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - New Hampshire Times, Aug./Sept. 1978 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - New Mobilizer, Sept. 5, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - New Orleans Baptist Theological Seminary Directory, 1963/1964 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - New Politics News, Nov. 1972 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - New Republic, Jun. 1965 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - New Republic, Oct. 1965 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - New Republic, Jan. 1979 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - New South, Apr. 1962- Sept. 1965 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - New South: Fall, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - New South: Fall, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - New South: Summer, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - “New Styles in Leftism” by Irving Howe (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - New University Thought Spring, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - New University Thought: Winter, 1966/1967 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - New York Viewpoint, Jun. 1965 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Newsweek, Mar. 11, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Newsweek, Mar. 18, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Newsweek, Mar. 25, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Newsweek, Apr. 1, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Newsweek, Apr. 22, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Newsweek, May 6, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Newsweek Newspointer, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - NOLA Express: nos. 1, 3, 4 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - NOLA Express: nos. 5, 6, 15 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - NOLA Express: nos. 16, 17, 18 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - NOLA Express: nos. 19-23 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - NOLA Express: nos. 24-28 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - NOLA Express: nos. 29-31 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - NOLA Express: nos.32-34 (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - NOLA Express: nos. 35, 36, 38 (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - NOLA Express: no. 40 and vol. 2 no. 1 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Off Our Backs: no. 10 (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - Off Our Backs: nos. 16, 18 (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Off Our Backs: no. 21 (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - Old Mole: nos. 21, 23 (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - Old Mole: nos. 28, 30 (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - Old Mole: no. 36 (Box 81, Folder 41)
  - On Studying World History (Box 81, Folder 42)
  - Open Letter to Activists and Organizers (Box 81, Folder 43)
  - Ossowatomie, Jun./Jul. 1976 (Box 81, Folder 44)
  - Pacific Currents, Aug. 1976 (Box 81, Folder 45)
  - Palante: vol. 3 no. 8 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Palestine Human Rights Bulletin, Aug. 30, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Palm, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Paper Bag: Vols. 1 and 2, Sept. 1968 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Password, Oct. 1987 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - PeaceCorps (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - People’s Appalachia: vol. 2 nos. 1, 2 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - People’s Voice: Feb. 26, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - People’s Press, May 1972 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - People’s World, Aug. 14, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - People’s Yellow Pages, Mar. 1972 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Polis, Jun. 1965 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Political Solutions: 1-4 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Political Solutions: 5-8 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Political Solutions: 9-12 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Political Solutions: 13-17 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Political Solutions: 18-20 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Popular Male Choruses (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Potomac: Spring, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Peace Reporter, Jan. 1968 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Practical Homeowner, Oct. 1989 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Progressive, May 1973 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Progressive Labor, May-Jun. 1965 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Protean, Mar.- Apr. 1969 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - “Psychological Effects of Poverty” by Ruth Kloepfer (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Preview, May 1981 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Profile: Autumn, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Public Life, Journal of Politics, Nov. 8, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Quantum, Sept. 1972 and Dec. 1972 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Rat, Apr. 1968 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Rat, Jul. 1968 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Rat, Sept. 1968 (Box 82, Folder 32)